Privacy Policy
--------------

This privacy policy will explain how our organization uses the personal data we collect from you when you use our website. The following topics are covered:

* Collected Information
* Data Collection
* Use of Personal Data
* Data Retention
* Data Storage
* Marketing
* Data Protection Rights
* Cookies
* Types of Cookies
* Cookie Management
* Privacy Policies of Other Web Sites
* Changes to Privacy Policy
* Contact Us

### Collected Information

We may collect and process the following categories of personal data:

* **Information You Provide:** When you interact with us, you may provide us with personal information such as your name, email address, postal address, phone number, and any other information you provide.
* **Automatically Collected Information:** We may automatically collect certain information about your device and usage of our website or services, including your IP address, browser type, operating system, referring URLs, access times, and pages visited.
* **Network metadata:** For customers subscribed to [Netify Informatics](https://www.netify.ai/products/netify-informatics), network metadata is collected to deliver the product solution. Please see the [Netify Agent documentation](https://www.netify.ai/resources/documentation/privacy) for details.

### Data Collection

You directly provide most of the data we collect. We collect data and process data when you:

* Register online or place an order for any of our products or services.
* Use or view our website via your optional browser's cookies.
* Installing the network agent for the [Netify Informatics](https://www.netify.ai/products/netify-informatics) product.

### Use of Personal Data

We may use your personal data for the following purposes:

* To provide and maintain our services.
* To respond to your inquiries, requests, and comments.
* To personalize your experience and tailor content and offerings to your interests.
* To improve our website and services and analyze usage trends.
* To communicate with you about our products, services, promotions, and events.
* To comply with legal and regulatory obligations.

### Data Retention

We securely store your data at our Toronto, Canada data center location. We will retain your personal data for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.

### Data Storage

Your data is stored securely in Canada and may be transferred to and processed in other countries where data protection laws may differ.

### Marketing

We may use your data for marketing purposes, but you have the right to opt-out of receiving marketing communications from us.

### Data Protection Rights

You have the right to request access, correction, erasure, or restriction of your personal data. You also have the right to object to processing of your personal data and to data portability.

### Cookies

We uses cookies in a range of ways to improve your experience on our website, including:

* Keeping you signed in
* Understanding how you use our website
* Contacting us via an online web form
* Live chat support

### Types of Cookies

There are a number of different types of cookies, however, our website uses:

* **Functionality** - We use these cookies so that we recognize you on our website and remember your previously selected preferences. These could include what language you prefer and location you are in. A mix of first-party and third-party cookies are used.
* **Analytics** - We use these cookies to collect information about your visit to our website, the content you viewed, the links you followed and information about your browser, device, and your IP address. We may share online data collected through cookies with our customer relationship partners.
* **Customer Relationship and Support** - We use these cookies for live chat and online form submissions.

### Cookie Management

You can manage cookies through your browser settings. Please note that if you refuse or delete cookies, some parts of our website may not function properly.

### Privacy Policies of Other Web Sites

Our website may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.

### Changes to Privacy Policy

We may update our privacy policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new privacy policy on this page.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of eGloo, or your dealings with this web site, you can contact [privacy@netify.ai](mailto:privacy@netify.ai).
